hey guys this looks like a fun one what
are the values of A and B such that a
plus b is equal to a times B which is
equal to a divided by B so let's do this
first thing I'm noticing is B cannot be
zero because of the a divided by B and
we can't have division by zero next
let's try a equal to zero let's look at
these two right here plug in zero for
both of these A's zero plus b is equal
to B and zero times B is equal to zero
so we have b equal to zero but we said
earlier B cannot equal zero so we have a
contradiction that means that a cannot
equal zero and we could put a boxer on
that let's get rid of this stuff and
bring this up here now let's look at a
times b equals a divided by B let's
rewrite it like this and multiply both
sides by B and on the right hand side
since these B's cancel we just have a b
times B is B squared so we have a times
B squared is equal to a if a divide both
sides by a we get B squared is equal to
one so that means there are two possible
values for B it could be positive one or
negative one for both scenarios let's
look at a plus b equals a times B for
both of these B's let's plug in one a
times one is eight so we end up with a
plus one equals a let's subtract a from
both sides on the left hand side we have
one and on the right hand side we have
zero so we end up with one equals zero
that is a contradiction that means that
b cannot equal one let's see what
happens when we plug in b equals
negative one we end up with a minus one
is equal to negative a now we can
subtract a from both sides we get
negative one equals negative two a
divide both sides by negative two we get
one half is equal to a and there's no
contradiction here so a equals one half
and b equals negative one this is our
solution how exciting